Trey Alexander | IT Intern

Location: Springfield, MO, 65804 Phone number: 417-761-2121 Email: treyaalex47@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/ArcadeRaven

GitHub Portfolio: TreyAlexanderPortfolio.github.io

My Personal Profile

Computer science graduate with a focus on Python and C++ development. I have worked in Agile and Waterfall methodologies across several teams to develop unique software. Unreal 5 engine experience and knowledge on landscaping, lighting, materials, textures, and blueprints.

With my time in an IT department and coding in teams, I am excellent at documentation, working in a team, collaborating with other teams, and getting work done without supervision. I am also able to troubleshoot errors and bugs, as well as understand code written by others.

Core Skills

Agile	Waterfall	Code Review
Network File Management	Documentation	GitHub
Python	C++	Unreal Engine 5

Highlighted Electives

- CSC 525: Graphic Rendering using C++ OpenGL and GLUT
- CSC 540: Introduction to Artificial Intelligence

Fluent Languages

- HTML and CSS
- Django
- Python
- C++
- PostgreSQL

Work Experience

September 2021 to Present – Toth and Associates

Title: IT Intern

- Working on user tickets to solve hardware and software related issues.
- Documenting solutions.
- Active Directory experience.
- Assisting remote users on calls.

November 2016 to September 2021 – Walgreens

Title: Pharmacy technician and "designated hitter"

- Worked in the pharmacy filling, selling, working at the drive through.
- Experience calling doctors and insurance companies to correct issues such as prior authorizations, incorrect dosages, and requests for refills.
- Prepared vaccinations for the pharmacist to administer to the patient.
- Customer service.
- Inventory management.
- Balancing time across multiple departments and responsibilities.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science – Missouri State University

Minor of Mathematics – Missouri State University AUGUST 2022

Projects

Solo development of a website for a local business myself using HTML and CSS. This website was rated second among 15 competing teams containing multiple members.

I created a website in a team-based, AGILE environment using HTML, CSS, and Django / Python for front-end and back-end integration. This project is in my portfolio.

I created a smart AI with a partner in Python that used the Minmax algorithm to play Pokémon Showdown. We used Pandas and a Pokémon-Showdown API. This project is in my portfolio.

Organizations and Hobbies

Missouri State League of Legends – Spring 2018 to Spring 2022